[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Put him in context, historical context, how important was Dick Clark, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, he was a pioneer, in the -- you know, in the early days of television, with \"American Bandstand,\" he revolutionized music on television.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Clark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What was the secret ingredient that he had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "He was a great generalist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Clark"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What was Dick's importance to you, your career and your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, there would have been no career without Dick Clark.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kari and Dick"], "LOCATION": ["Malibu"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Do you think in the end that he realized that wasn't what was important to his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "RANCIS: Well, it was really up until -- I think I saw him a year and a half ago, I went to visit Kari and Dick in Malibu, their home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What was the importance of \"American Bandstand\" to any young musical act in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "It was the show that everybody wanted to be on because it presented their talent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "How many people -- of all the people that you ever interviewed had that distinctive, gut feel for what the majority of Americans would love to see or hear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I have to think of it -- Steve Jobs, interviewed him early on, he had it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Marie Show"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Was that your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Actually, Piers, I got an experience that \"Donny and Marie Show.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Clark"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "What did he do, how was he in that persuasive mode?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, I got to tell you, I think only Dick Clark could have talked me into doing that, because, you know, twice in my life my knees have knocked, and that was one of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What was it about him that enabled him to persuade people they had the confidence to do stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "He was an every man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", ":", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What do you think America has lost today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "They have lost an institution, when these -- when these people leave us, they leave a hole that doesn't get filled.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "How big a moment is that for any musical act?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Think I appreciate it now more than I did then, because back then, we were still very much kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", ":", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "William, he says it all there, Lionel, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "EX", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "You know, the thing is that I remember one time we first met, he kept saying gentlemen, gentlemen to us, because -- say that to us.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Lionel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "And did you realize at the time what a big deal it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "You know, I did realize.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Is it a stretch to say that Dick Clark played a really significant and valuable role in the civil rights movement because of the way that he brought black performers and black bands and music to mainstream American television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I don't think it's a stretch at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Clark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What was it about him, do you think, that made him so universally popular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I think it is what the guys were saying, that he didn't put his own opinion -- he really represented the music that America loved and wanted to hear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "He was really, as Larry King and others said earlier, pretty unique and pretty irreplaceable, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "He was sprinkling, you know, this magical dust of sorts across television with award shows and reality shows and game shows.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry King"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I think a lot of people in the television industry do feel like he's the closest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]